printerland.co.uk 2018-12-13

# About Us - Printerland.co.uk

Welcome to Printerland.co.uk - the UK's Largest Printer and Consumable Reseller

With over 12,000 products to choose from, Printerland.co.uk provides everything you need to find your perfect printer. We have all the latest line-ups from the print industry's leading manufacturers such as Xerox, Lexmark, HP and Epson along with all the genuine manufacturer approved toner and ink supplies to keep your print fleet running at maximum productivity.

We understand that choosing the best printer for your business can be a difficult decision and that's why we employ over 30 of the best printer experts around to help you find a device that meets your business requirements, fits your budget and keeps your ongoing costs down.

Our continued success is due to our commitment to ensure you get the best product at the lowest price and in the quickest time possible.

* * *

## Why Choose Printerland.co.uk?

### Over 30 printer experts waiting to talk to you

Our Office in Cheshire is home to the best manufacturer trained printer experts in the country

### Our Customers Love Us!

Join thousands of happy customers today and enjoy the best service your business deserves

### Free Next Day Delivery on all orders over £125 ex VAT

Our express courier service ensures your order arrives in the quickest time possible

25

### Over 25 Years of Trusted Service

We were established in 1993 and have grown to be the largest independent reseller of printers and consumables in the UK

£££

### Lowest Price Guaranteed

We check our competitors every day to ensure you get the best deal without having to shop around

### Proud to be a UK Tax-Payer

Printerland is registered in England and Wales with a UK based call centre, making it even easier to get the support you need

* * *

## Printerland in the Community

Printerland is proud to have an ongoing commitment to providing support in and around the local community. From our sponsorship of local charity events to providing opportunities for youngsters in schools and organisations around the country, we continue to share our success with those who need our support the most. For the latest events and press excerpts please visit our news page here: [Printerland in the News.](https://www.printerland.co.uk/PrinterlandNews.aspx)

In 2016, Printerland.co.uk renewed its partnership with Sale Sharks Rugby Union Club by sponsoring the Family Stand at the AJ Bell Stadium. As long-time supporters of Sale Sharks the company sponsored the famous Cheadle end of the club's previous home ground Edgely Park and were part of the corporate family that helped to build sell-out crowds and a premiership winning team in 2006.

Printerland.co.uk co-owner Graham Vickers commented, "It's great to be back involved with Sale Sharks. We do a lot of work with our local community and schools in the region and we look forward to extending our partnership with the Sharks to support these projects and introduce Rugby to a new audience that may not previously have had the chance to attend a match."

* * *

## Making a Purchase

Making a purchase could not be easier. Just browse our Catalogue, when you find the item you wish to purchase click on the Add To Cart Button. You now have the choice to confirm and continue shopping, or checkout now and continue to pay for your purchase where you will be asked for a few details that we need to be able to satisfy the order.

Should you wish to purchase over the phone, call us on 0800 840 1992. We accept Visa, Mastercard, Switch, American Express and Delta cards or you can pay by cheque or bank transfer. PayPal, Amazon Payments and Google Checkout have also been provided should you wish to use an alternative checkout method.Accounts are available for Government Bodies and Educational Establishments.

## International Orders

Printerland.co.uk accepts international orders. For more information on how to place an order from outside the United Kingdom please refer to the following terms: International Orders

## Shipping And Handling

Free next business day delivery is available on all printers and orders over £125.00 + VAT on the UK mainland. We also deliver to the Channel Islands, Scottish Islands, Isle of Man, Northern Ireland and Eire. For our delivery charges please click the following link: Delivery Charges

## Delivery Schedule

We process your order right away. We will normally send your order to you by next business day service, if your order is placed before 4:30PM. No guarantees are given for next day delivery. However, our mission is to achieve this where possible.

## Back Orders

should your item not be in stock, we will back order for you. You will always be emailed with the option to cancel your order or choose an alternative product if you would rather not wait.

## Credit Card Security

All credit card numbers are encrypted and we hold no credit card information on our servers. We incorporate the best possible security measures throughout our checkout process and we are proud to be an accredited ISIS ('Internet Shopping Is Safe') retailer ensuring that your shopping experience with us is as worry free as possible.

## Guarantee

All printers, consumables and accessories are genuine items warranted by their associated manufacturer. If you receive a faulty item or an item becomes faulty, please contact us and we will resolve the issue to your satisfaction.

## Recycling

We are pleased to offer our customers the chance to recycle their old electrical items when purchasing a new item from us. 

The Waste Electrical or Electronic Equipment (WEEE) Directive requires countries to maximise separate collection and environmentally friendly processing of these items. In the UK, distributors (including retailers) must provide a system which allows all customers buying new electrical equipment the opportunity to recycle their old items free of charge. 

When making your purchase, please speak to one of our experts for details on how to dispose of your WEEE item with us. Alternatively you can email us at [recycling@printerland.co.uk](mailto:recycling@printerland.co.uk) for more details.

To remind you that old electrical equipment can be recycled, it is now marked with a crossed‐out wheeled bin symbol. Please do not throw any electrical equipment (including those marked with the crossed out wheeled bin symbol) in your bin.

* * *

## Privacy Policy

### Visitors to our website

When someone visits this website we use a third party service called google Analytics to collect standard, anonymous user data and internet log information to help us analyse the number of visitors who browse various parts of our website. We do this in order to help us make improvements to our service and to help make your future visits easier. We do not allow Google to access any personally identifiable information of our visitors. 

We also use some smaller third party tools in order to gather survey data to help us understand the needs of our users over time. This data is also gathered anonymously and your personal details are not passed on. 

Where we do have to gather your personal information, such as delivery and invoicing details you will be in control of inputting those details and you will always do so via a secure, encrypted page which keeps your information private.

We do not disclose buyers' information to third parties unless required for order processing purposes.

Cookies are used on this shopping site to keep track of the contents of your shopping cart once you have selected an item. No personal information is held using cookies.

The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. For more information please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.printerland.co.uk/Cookies-E363.aspx).

### Special Offers and Coupon Code e-mails

When placing an order with us you will be asked whether you wish to receive our special offers and coupon codes via email. We use a third party in order to send these emails to you and we use the resulting statistics gathered via standard technologies in order to help us improve these emails for you.

Once you have requested enrolment, you are free to use the unsubscribe links contained in each of these emails at any time. Alternatively you can email us directly via [privacy@printerland.co.uk](mailto:privacy@printerland.co.uk?subject=Unsubscribe) and our team will manually remove you from this list on your behalf.

### People who place an order with us

For the purposes of processing your order and delivering your items, your personal information is gathered during the checkout process on the website or directly with our sales team if placing the order by telephone. This data is passed to our third party suppliers and couriers strictly in order for us to provide the service you have asked us to supply to you. These parties are acting as data processors and will only use your personal information in line with our instructions.

### Access to your personal information

Printerland wishes to be as transparent as possible in terms of giving access to any personal information we may hold about you. Individuals can request, if we hold any information about them by submitting a ‘subject access request’ under the data protection act 1998. If we do hold any information about you, we will:

  1. Provide a description of it
  2. Give a reason as to why we hold it
  3. Tell you who it could be disclosed to
  4. Provide you with a copy of the data in an intelligible form

To submit a ‘subject access request’, you can make a formal request in writing to the address provided below. If you agree, we will try to deal with your request directly with you by providing the information you need over the telephone. If we do hold your information you can ask us to correct any mistakes at this point or by a formal written response.

### Right to be forgotten

You always have the option to request the removal of your data from our systems at any point by providing a written request to the address below.

Computer Risk Management (Trading as Printerland.co.uk), is registered in England & Wales and is a UK Tax payer.

Printerland the mark, has been registered under the Trade Mark Act 1994 of Great Britain & Northern Ireland under No.2385571
